Guide to the Records of Jewish Culture Foundation RG.12.11
New York University Archives
Records of the Jewish Culture Foundation
1929-2001
1955-1990
New York University Archives
Jewish Culture Foundation
RG.12.11
7.1 Linear Feet
The Jewish Culture Foundation was a student group at NYU, and its records relate to the organization's administration and functions.
Provenance
The first part of the records were transferred to the University Archives in 1981 by Naomi Olkon, who was the director of the Jewish Culture Foundation at that time. In 2010, the second half of the collection was moved to the University Archives and integrated with the earlier materials.
Access Restrictions
Institutional records of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation (the date on which each document was written). Board of Trustees records are similarly closed for 35 years from the date of creation. The opening date for files spanning several years will be 20 years from the most recent date. Access will be given to material already 20 years old contained within a collection that is not yet open when such material can be isolated from the rest of the collection.
Materials related to personnel, faculty grievances, job searches and all files with information that falls under the University's Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) policy are permanently restricted.
Historical Note
The Jewish Culture Foundation was founded in 1937 by Abraham Katsh, chairman of the Department of Hebrew Culture and Education at NYU. Its goal was to serve the religious, cultural, and social needs of the Jewish student body on both the University Heights and Washington Square campuses. The group lobbied for kosher dining and university breaks on Jewish holidays and also organized events for Jewish holidays. They published the Shofar Press, NYU Pride, and Te'chiyat Hanefesh.
Scope and Content Note
The Jewish Culture Foundation was an NYU student organization representing and serving the Jewish students on campus. The collection covers the social, political and financial activities of the organization from its founding in 1937 until 2001, when student members were involved in relief efforts relating to September 11, 2001. The records include correspondence, budgets, election information, event flyers, calendars, JCF and related publications, and information about Jewish groups at other institutions.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically within series.
The files are grouped into four series:
Series
I: Correspondence
II: Events and Programs
III: Publications
IV: Subject Files
Related Material at the New York University Archives
See Photograph Collections, Individual Collections, Box 12, Jewish Culture Foundation.
See RG 39.9, Series 7 for publications associated with the Jewish Culture Foundation and RG 39.9.1 for the Jewish Culture Foundation's Women's Division.
See RG 42.9 for records of the Bronfman Center for Jewish Life Galleries at NYU.
Jewish college students.; Jews |x Dietary laws.; Judaism.; Passover.; September 11 Terrorist Attacks, 2001.; Fasts and feasts |x Judaism.; United Jewish Appeal; Rudavsky, David.; Marke, Julius J.; Winter, Nathan H.; New York University; Payne, E. George (Enoch George), 1877-1953; Osserman, Wendy; Hebrew Union College-Jewish Institute of Religion; Katsh, Abraham Isaac, 1908-1998
- Series I: Administrative
  - Subseries A: Correspondence
    - Audit, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Board of Trustees, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - From the Director's Office, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - From the Director's Office, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - To the Director's Office, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - To the Director's Office, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Edelman, Ethel, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Edelman, Irvin A. Estate, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Edelman, Richard, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Finances, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Franklin, Naomi, Director, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Fundraising, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - General, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - General, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - General, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - General, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - General, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Glick, Carl, 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Israel Independence Day, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - JCF Building, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - JCF Building, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - JCF Building--RESTRICTED, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - JCF Building--RESTRICTED, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - JCF Building, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Kahn, William Federation of Jewish Philanthropies, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Katsch, Abraham, 1929-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Katsch, Abraham, 1938-1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Katsch, Abraham, 1956-1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Katsch, Abraham, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Korn, Edward, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Lieberman, Judge Abraham, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Maggin, Jane C., 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Marke, Julius J., 1960 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - NYU Faculty, Israel, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - NYU Press Releases, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - NYU Pride, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Olkin, Naomi, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Parshelsky Foundation, 1978-1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Passover, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Payne, E. George, Assistant Dean, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Pollack, David, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Press Releases, 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Protection Services, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Publicity Sources, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Related Organizations, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Religious Excuse, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Rosenthal Library Fellowship, 1974-1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Rudavsky, David, Treasurer, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Rudavsky, David, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Solomon, Louis H., Last Will and Testament, 1959-1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Solomon, Louis H., Last Will and Testament, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Student Surveys, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Winter, Nathan, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence--RESTRICTED, 1929-1986 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      Scope and Contents
      This folder contains restricted material that was removed from Box 2, folders 3, 4, 5, 7, 12, 13, 15, 16, 17, and 20.
  - Subseries B: Minutes and Reports
    - Activities, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Activities, 1961-1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Activities, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Activities, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Activities, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Activities, Spring 1977 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Activities, 1977 Spring (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Activities, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Annual Reports, 1951-1964 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Annual Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Board of Trustees, 1971-1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Board of Trustees, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Director's Reports, 1985-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Director of Student Activities, 1956-1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Executive Board, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Executive Board, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Donations, 1966-1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Final Report, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - General, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - General, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - General, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Graduate and Alumni Group, 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Guard's Reports (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Interfaith Council, 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Interfaith Council, 1959-1962 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Interfaith Council, 1965-1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Interfaith Council, 1969-1970, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Officer's Meeting, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Progress Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Publicity (I), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Publicity (II), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Student Executive Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Summaries and Calendars, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - To Do Lists, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Subseries C: Financial and Legal Materials
    - All-Square Student Budget Committee, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - All-Square Student Budget Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - All-Square Student Budget Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - All-Square Student Budget Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Bequests, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 1959-1963 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Budget, 1975-1981 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Budget, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Budget: Projected, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Budget: Proposed, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Budget: Proposed, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Building Fund, 1966, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Building Fund: Pledges, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1954-1956 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Club Treasurer Materials, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Edelman Estate, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Edelman Professorship, 1972-1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Expenses, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Expenses, 1987-1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Expenses: Student Activities, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Contributions, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Financial Log, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Fundraising, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Funds, 1957-1960 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Funds, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Funds: Appeals, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Goldman, A. Robert, Estate, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Goldsmith, Horace W., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Goldsmith Center, 1974-1981 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Goldsmith Fund, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Goldsmith Memorial Fund, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Goldsmith Memorial Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Goldsmith Trust, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Goldsmith Trust, circa 1980 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Incorporation, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Israel Bonds, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Lippman Estate, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Operating Fund, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Parshelsky Foundation, 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Parshelsky Foundation, 1959-1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Property, JCF, 1978-1986 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Property Sale, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Rudavsky, David, 1975-1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Sale of 64-66 West 3rd Street, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Student Activities: Club Treasurer Materials, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Tax Exemption Status, 1971-1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Wills: Solomon, Louis H., 1975-1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Wills and Bequests, 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Subseries D: Related Organizations
    - Breira, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Distribution Materials, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Israel Students Organization, 1956-1960 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Jewish Association for College Youth, 1971-1985 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Jewish Association for College Youth, 1972-1978 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Jewish Association for College Youth, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Association for College Youth, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Jewish Association for College Youth, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Jewish Association for College Youth, 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Jewish Association for College Youth: Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Jewish Association for College Youth: Budget, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Association for College Youth: Grants, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Student Appeal, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Jewish Student Appeal: Campaign Guide, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Jewish Student Appeal: Financial, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Jewish Student Appeal: Report, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Jewish Student Appeal: Resources, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Jewish Student Appeal: Solicitation Handbook, Undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - United Jewish Appeal: Campaign Guide, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Women's Division: Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Women's Division: Distribution Materials, 1980s (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Women's Division: Fundraising, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Women's Division: General, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Women's Division: Gifts, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Women's Division: Membership, 1964-1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Women's Division: Membership, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Series II: Events and Programs
  - Subseries I: Planning Materials
    - Advertising, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Amsterdam, Judge Birdie, Dinner, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Anniversary Dinner, 25th, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Banquet, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Banquet, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Book Fair, 1965-1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Calendars, 1939-1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Ceremonial Object Labels, Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Chabad Special Events, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Comedy Event 3/19/02, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Edelman Lecture Series, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Elections, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - El Salvador Alternative Spring Break, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Film Series, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Film Series, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Free University of Judaism, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Freshman Orientation, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - General, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - General, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Guest List, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Gold Key Merit Awards and Donors, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Holocaust Memorial Week, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Holocaust Program, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Holocaust Symposium (I), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Holocaust Symposium (II), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Hornstein Tribute Dinner, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Kosher Kitchen, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Kosher Kitchen, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Israel Beckons Workshop, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Israel Independence Day, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Israel Independence Day, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Israel Independence Day Rally, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Israel, Land of the Bible Lecture Series, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Israel Night of Stars, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Israel Trip, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Jewish Comedy Website, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Jewish Student Campaign, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Lapid Café, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Lecture: Dayan, Moshe, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Lectures, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Osserman Wendy, Dance Performances, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Passover, 1958-1962 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Passover, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Program for Leadership and Service in the Sixties, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Purim (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - September 11th Benefit Concert, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Shabbotton, 1970-1975, Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Songbook Permissions, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Soviet Jewry, Greater New York Conference, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Spitzer Forum, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Student Mobilization for Israel, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Succot, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Tribute to E. George Payne, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Subseries II: Distribution Materials
    - Anniversary, 25th, circa 1964 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Chug Yisael, circa 1978 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - General, 1930s-1940s (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - General, 1960-1967 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - General, 1960-1978 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - General, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - General, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - General, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - General, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - General, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - General, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - General (I), 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - General (II), 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - General, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - General, 1979-1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - General, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - General, 1990s (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - General, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Mailing Lists, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Mailing Lists, Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Mailings, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Passover, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Payne, George Dinner, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Rogosin, Israel, Dinner, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Student Newspaper Ads, 1969-1970, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Series III: Publications
  - The American Hebrew, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Articles of Interest, 1971-1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - The Flame, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Forum, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Forum: Letterheads, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Culture Voice, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Culture Voice: Articles, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Press Release: Articles, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Student Press Service (I), 1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Student Press Services (II), 1971 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Newsletter, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - New York Jewish Experience, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - The Pride: Articles, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - The Pride: Articles, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - The Pride, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Shofar, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - The Source, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Student, 1973-1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Student, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Student Acitivties, Office of, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Te'chiyat Hanefesh (I), 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Te'chiyat Hanefesh (II), 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Te'chiyat Hanefesh (III), 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Te'chiyat Hanefesh: Articles, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Series IV: Subject Files
  - Background, JCF, 1947, Undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Black Americans Support Israel, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - B'nai B'rith Hillel Foundations, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Board Information (President's File), 1974-1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Building Space Needs, 1961-1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Bylaws, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Center for Jewish Culture, circa 1950-1960 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1957-1962 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Committees, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Constitution, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Crafts, Undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Description, JCF, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Elections, JCF, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Exams on Jewish Holidays, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Council, Undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Films, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Gottesman Library of Judaica and Hebraica, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Hannukah, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Hebrew Union College: Jewish Institute of Religion, Undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - History, 1958-1975 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - History and Founding, 1938-1943 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - History and Founding, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Holocaust, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Holocaust Haggadah, 1970s (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Peace Fellowship, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Katsh, Abraham, 1955, Undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Kosher Dining, 1967-1972 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kosher Meal Plan, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kosher Meal Plan, 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Library, 1972-1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Logo, Undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Modern Language Association, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - National Association of Professors of Hebrew, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Plotkin, Rabbi, 1981-1991 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Room 709, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Rudavsky, David, Educational Articles, Undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - September 11th Materials, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Synagogue, 1963-1967 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Synagogue "21", 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Synagogue/Meditation Room, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Syrian Jews, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 20)